The next step we have here is to find a bucket.
This is a professional window washing bucket.
It works great because you can have a long sponge and stick it in there without having a whole lot of water in the bucket.
That is why they are elongated like that.
Second if you are just doing this around the house and you want something to use, I just got this from Home Depot, any old bucket will do.
The problem you find with some of these buckets if you are trying to get your sponge wet, sometimes you have to stick it in one side and dip it in the other and that is why these other buckets are handy.
And this bucket I have is what I keep my equipment in.
You an pick this up at a cleaning supply store for $15 to $20.
It has a spot for your sponge and a spot for your squeegee and you can put two or three different size squeegees in there.
If you are going to be doing this full time professionally, you definitely want to invest in something like this.